(加拿大西北部 1845年)
你真是体弱多病
You're always sick.
你以前还不是一样
You were sick when you were my age.
晚上好 先生
Evening, sir.
晚上好 维克多
Evening, Victor.
我没有想到你还会在这里
I didn't realize that you're still here.
我只是在陪詹姆斯 先生
I'm just keeping James company, sir.
如果可以的话...
If that's all right...
你真贴心
Very kind of you.
- 你有好点吗 儿子? - 还是很冷 爸爸
- Are you better, son? - Still cold, father.
只是轻度发烧 早上起来就会好了
It's just a mild fever, you'll be all right in the morning.
你总是那样说
You always say that.
你也总是会好呀 难道不是吗?
And you always pull through, don't you?
现在... 吃药吧
Now... take your medicine.
伊莉莎白！
Elizabeth.
Elizabeth
你爸爸又喝醉了
Your father's drunk again.
你该带他回家 维克多
You should help him home, Victor.
他找的人又不是我 先生
It's not my name he's calling, sir.
- 爸爸! - 待在床上 儿子!
- Father! - Stay where you are, James!
爸爸!
Father!
我告诉过你 永远不要再回到这里!
I told you never to come back here!
詹姆斯
James...
有一些你不懂的事
There are things you don't understand.
- 别... - 我需要他知道!
- Don't... - I need him to know!
请不要!
Please no!
不再有... 更多的... 谎言!
No... more... lies!
詹姆斯
James..
James!
他... 他不是你的爸爸...
He... he wasn't your father...
儿子
son.
你是什么怪物?
What are you?
- 我不是故意的! 我不是... - 你就是!
- I didn't mean it! I didn't... - Yes, you did!
他罪有应得! 所以你杀了他
He deserved it! And you gave it to him.
我们是兄弟 你明白吗?
We're brothers, Jimmy. You realize that?
兄弟会彼此扶持
Brothers protect each other.
你现在必须要坚强
You have to be hard now.
坚强到他们甚至无法对我们动手
Hard enough they can't ever touch us.
我想回家
I want to go home.
不行
We can't.
无论如何 我们都要形影不离
We stick together no matter what.
干掉任何阻碍我们的人
And take care of anyone who gets in our way.
你能做到吗 小弟？
Can you do that, little brother?
他们追来了 你能跑吗? 好的
They're coming. Can you run? Okay.
一直跑 不要回头看
Keep on running. Don't look back.
背对背
Back-to-back.
够了
That's  enough.
Enough.
住手 士兵!
Stand down, soldier!
住手!
Stand down!
维克多 不要!
Victor, no!
预备!
Ready!
瞄准!
Aim!
结束时叫醒我
Wake me when it's over.
射击!
Fire!
《金刚狼》
我是威廉史崔克少校
My name is Major William Stryker.
你们被指控谋杀了一位高级军官
You have been charged of killing of a senior officer.
是那样吗?
Is that correct?
我们明显和当局有一些争端
Apparently we have some issues with authority.
不要再说了
Just keep a lid on it.
长官
Sir.
监狱长告诉我 你们的判决...
The warden tells me that your sentence was carried out...
早就由行刑队执行了
by a firing squad at 1000 hours.
- 那进行得怎样? - 觉得痒
- How'd that go? - It tickled.
你们厌倦了亡命天涯?
You boys tired of running?
厌倦否认你们的... 本性?
Tired of denying your... true nature?
- 你关心什么? - 喔 我关心...
- What do you care? - Oh, I care...
我关心 因为我知道你们多么与众不同...
I care cause I know how special you are...
多有价值
how valuable.
听着
Look.
你们可以待在这 像怪物一样被锁着...
You can stay here, locked up like freaks of nature...
或者你们可以加入我
or you can join me.
我正在组织一支特殊的团队...
I'm putting together a special team...
有着特权
with special privileges.
现在来告诉我...
Now tell me...
你想要怎样真正地为你的国家服务?
How would you like to really serve your country?
普天之下 我最喜欢这件武器了
I love this weapon more than anything in the whole wide world.
- 你想知道为什么吗? - 不
- You wanna know why? - No.
它是有纪念意义的
It's memorable.
当然了 把它们带上飞机 是有一点庞大
Sure, it's a little bulky, to have to get 'em on a plane.
你抽出了几把刀...
You whip out a couple of swords...
在你前女友的婚礼上...
at your ex-girlfriend's wedding...
他们永远也不会 忘记这件事
they will never, ever forget it.
真是怪了
That's funny, Wade.
我想你错认为 我是可以跟你胡扯的人
I think you confuse me with someone who gives you the shit.
对 那是...
Right, it is...
这或许没有一把枪那么吓人 或者...
it's probably not as intimidating as having a gun or...
露宿街头的女人那满是骨头的脚爪或指甲...
bone claws or the fingernails of a bag lady...
- 修指甲? - 维克多... 放轻松
- Manicure? - Victor... easy.
佛雷纹了新的刺青 我很担心
Fred got a new tattoo. I'm concerned.
噢 天啊 佛雷 你昨晚才碰到他
Oh geez, Fred, you just met her last night.
- 我爱她 - 一夜之后 你就爱上她?
- I love her. - You love her after one night?
她是一位体操运动员
She's a gymnast.
布莱德 降落吧
Bradley, take her down.
你要吐吗?
Are you gonna puke?
如果我们想飞的话 我们会长出翅膀的
If we were meant to fly, we'd have grown wings.
喔 别担心 瞧 更多的人死于车祸 而不是飞机失事
Oh, don't worry man. See, more people die driving than flying.
刺穿怎么样呢?
How about from impaling?
嘿 友好一点 或你所认为的友好
Hey, be nice. Or your approximation of nice.
你想要一个水桶吗?
Would you like a bucket?
各位 五分钟之后 飞机就会降落到拉各斯(尼日利亚首都)
Gentlemen, wheels down in Lagos in five.
(尼日利亚 拉各斯)
- 我们为什么在这里? - 待会儿就知道了 零号特工...
- Why are we here? - All in good time. Zero...
- 维克多 高处的瞭望台 - 很有乐趣?
- Victor, high ground lookout. - Having fun yet?
- 佛雷... - 坦克?
- Fred... - Tank?
- 对 - 没问题
- Tank. - Yeah, I got that.
很好!
Great!
和五个吃高蛋白质饮食的人一起被困在电梯里
Stuck in an elevator with five guys on a high protein diet.
- 喔 韦德! - 梦想真的可以成真
- Oh Wade! - Dreams really do come true.
闭嘴! 接着到你上去
Would you just shut it! You're up next.
谢谢 长官 你今天气色真好
Thank you, sir. You look very nice today.
那是苍白而已
It's the green.
严肃一点
Brings out the seriousness in your eyes.
噢 我的天 你是不是没有停止过讲话啊 兄弟?
Oh my God, do you ever shut up, pal?
不 我醒的时候 没停止过
No, not when I'm awake.
布莱德? 顶楼 拜托了
Bradley? Top floor, please.
瞄准电梯! 电梯!
Cover the elevator! The elevator!
工作时间到
Time to go to work.
好的!
Okay!
人都死了!
People are dead!
如果你没有那张嘴 韦德...
If you haven't that mouth on you, Wade...
你将会是一位完美的士兵
you'd be the perfect soldier.
拿走钻石 都归你们了
Take the diamonds, they're yours.
我不想要你的钻石
I don't want your diamonds.
我想要这个
I want this.
那? 那一文不值 一个纪念品
That? That is nothing. A souvenir.
你在哪里找到它? 我想要它的来源
Where did you find it? I want the source.
一个小村庄 内陆深处 距这里三天路程
A small village, far inland, three days from here.
跟他说 在我眼里 这块石头比他的命更有价值
Tell him that this rock is more valuable to me than his life.
问他 在哪找到的
Ask him where he found it.
他说 那是从天上掉下来的
He says it came from the sky.
他讲的是真话
He's telling the truth.
你不会他们的语言 罗根
You don't know their language, Logan.
是陨石
It's a meteor fragment.
我知道它是什么
I know what it is.
我问的是 他在哪儿找到它
I'm asking him where he found it.
长官 基地想要知道我们的位置
Sir, base wants to know our location.
让他闭嘴
Shut him down.
告诉他 这里的每一个人都会死...
Tell him everyone here will die...
除非他告诉我 他在哪找到这石头的
unless he tells me where he found the rock.
- 他说那是神圣的 - 好的 行
- He said that is sacred. - Okay, fine.
维克多
Victor...
想都不要想!
Don't even think about it!
我们并没有签约干这种事
We didn't sign up for this.
放开他
Put him down.
你在做什么啊?
What are you doing?
我们终于要在这里做成好事了
We finally got a good thing going here.
你不要把这搞砸了
Don't you screw this up.
够了 这已经够了 我们已做得够多了
Enough, it's enough. We've done enough.
你以为你是谁啊?
Who do you think you are?
这就是我们所做的
This is what we do.
或许你宁愿在一个洞穴里慢慢腐烂
Maybe you'd rather be rotting in a hole somewhere
直到他们想出对付我们的方法 是这样吗?
till they figure out a way to do it to us, is that it?
嗯?
Uh?
我不干了
I'm done.
你也走吗?
You coming?
吉米！
Jimmy!
我们不能就这样让你离开!
We can't just let you walk away!
吉米！
Jimmy!
(加拿大落基山脉 6年后)
怎么起得这么早?
Why are you up so early?
过来
Come here.
回见 宝贝
See you baby.
噢 好甜蜜啊! 是的!
Oh, that's nice! Yeah!
(俄亥俄州 春田市)
哦 去那边
No. Come on.
嗨 你这有什么玩意?
Hey, what do you do?
把灯关掉 就有大奖
You turn off the light, you win a prize.
- 1块钱2次 - 来吧 我要玩!
- Two tries for a buck. - Come on, I wanna do it!
嗯 必须釜底抽薪了
Um, that's obvious.
2次了
That's two.
- 这个玩笑可不怎么样 - 这不是玩笑 伙计
- That's a stupid trick. - It's not a trick, man.
我们走
Come on.
怪物
Freak.
拜!
Bye!
表演结束了!
Show's over!
我说了 表演结束了!
I said, show's over!
我们的表演永远不会结束 布莱德
The show is never over for us, Bradley.
- 维克多 - 不请我进来坐坐吗?
- Victor. - Aren't you gonna invite me in?
对 赶紧进来吧
Yeah, come on in.
你知道的 我什么都没说过...
You know, I've never said anything...
没有对任何人... 提起过那件事
to anyone... about what happened.
我现在过着一种全新的生活 我不需要...
I'm living a totally different life now, but uh...
再像过去那样
No need to bring up the past.
知道么
You know,
我总想会是韦德首先来找我
I always thought it would be Wade coming knocking at my door.
不幸的是 韦德已经死了
Well, Wade's gone.
我不怕你 维克多
I'm not afraid of you, Victor.
我不怕死
I'm not afraid to die.
你怎么知道? 你又没有试过
How do you know? You've never tried it before.
又梦到打仗了?
Was it the wars?
- 哪次? - 全部
- Which one? - All of them.
给我说说吧
Tell me.
一点抓痕而已
It's just a scratch.
看来我们又得买新被单了 宝贝
Looks like we're gonna need new sheets again, baby.
是的...
Yeah...
这些人是谁?
Who the hell is this?
政府来找麻烦了
It smells like government.
我的天! 你一点也没老!
My God! Haven't aged a day!
无忧无虑嘛
Clean living.
还记得零号特工探员吗
You remember Agent Zero.
你依然先拔枪后问话吗?
Still shooting first and asking questions later?
你还在抽这种便宜的雪茄吗?
You still chewing those cheap cigars?
伙计们 别闹了 我这有个工作你干不干
Boys, please. I have a job for you.
- 我已经有工作了 - 伐木工
- I already have a job. - Lumberjack.
- 1万8一年? - 1万8千5
- Eighteen grand a year? - Eighteen five.
另外这些日子还不用杀人
Plus I haven't had to kill anyone in a while.
- 开始怀念了吗? - 是的 现在想
- Start to miss it? - Yeah, right now I am.
零号特工 回车里去
Zero, back to the car.
很好
Attaboy.
你知道吗 以这种方式结束我们之间的合作 让我深感不快
You know, I'm not proud about the way things ended between us.
谈话结束
Conversation's over.
跟一个乡村教师厮守与大草原中的...
Play the little house on the prairie with a...
一个小房子里
a school teacher.
这可不是你啊 罗根
That's just isn't you, Logan.
你想知道吗 哼?
And you would know, huh?
我想
I would.
你到底想怎样 史崔克?
What do you want, Stryker?
布莱德三天前被杀了
Bradley was killed three days ago.
韦德在这之前也惨遭不幸
Wade, before that.
我确信有人正在抓捕我们的队员
I believe that someone is hunting down our whole team.
还有谁死了吗?
Anyone else?
就目前所知 维克多没事
As far as I know, Victor is safe.
- 不管是谁 总要留下蛛丝马迹的... - 我能照顾好我自己
- Whoever it is, he's had names, addresses... - I can take care of myself.
你不要这么自私 罗根
This is not about you, Logan.
国家需要你
Country needs you.
我不是美国人
I am Canadian.
我很清楚 罗根! 我很清楚你是谁!
I know you, Logan! I know who you are!
怎么了?
What's wrong?
史崔克今天来过了
Stryker came by today.
别担心 我拒绝了
Don't worry, I said no.
这么多年过去了 他怎么还来骚扰你?
Why is he bothering you after all these years?
因为在那我是干的最好的
Because I'm the best there is at what I do.
但是杀人的感觉并不好
And what I do best isn't very nice.
你不是野兽 罗格 你所拥有的是与生俱来的天赋
You're not an animal, Logan. What you have is a gift.
天赋?
A gift?
宁愿不要这种天赋
You can return a gift.
快点吧 伙计!
Come on, fellas!
- 别处去了 - 我不会动粗的
- Stay in the car. - I'm just gonna ask nicely.
让我们过去一下好吗?
Mind lettin' us go by?
你有急事吗 朋友?
You're in some kind of a hurry there, pal?
有吗?
Are ya?
把你的车挪一点 我们就可以过去了...
Just move your truck so we can go by...
来谈谈吧 伙计
Trying to have a conversation there, right.
事都已经这样了...
If you start something...
你还想敷衍了事吗
you'd better be ready to finish it.
伙计们 别冲动!
Hey guys, take it easy!
你男朋友废话太多了
Your boyfriend's got a big mouth.
我知道
I know.
你的脾气也大了点 让我们过去 好吗
Big temper too, so please, let us pass.
谢谢!
Thank you!
你怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
说服别人 也是一种天赋
You know, power of persuasion is a gift.
明白了 你的那些能力... 嗯 怎么对我没起作用?
I see, do you... uh, have those powers over me?
你不是没呆在车里吗?
Well, you didn't stay in the car, did you?
月儿为何如此孤寂？
Why is the moon so lonely?
为什么?
Why?
因为她曾经一个爱人
Because she used to have a lover.
- 你对孩子们就这样说的? - 不是
- You tell this to the kids? - No.
他的名字叫库埃阿苏...
His name was Kuekuatsheu...
他们一起生活在神界之中
and they lived in the spirit world together.
- 噢 这是真的 - 是的
- Ah, it's a true story. - Right.
每晚 他们都会一起在天空中漫步
And every night, they would wander the skies together.
可是... 其中的一位神灵心生嫉妒
But... one of the other spirits was jealous.
崔克斯特想独占月儿
Trickster, one of the moons from South,
他告诉奎库阿苏月儿想要人间美丽的鲜花
so he told Kuekuatsheu that the moon had asked for flowers.
他怂恿库埃阿苏来到了人间...
He told him to come to our world...
然后他采摘了一堆野玫瑰...
and pick up some wild roses...
可库埃阿苏不知道的是...
But Kuekuatsheu didn't know...
一旦离开神界...
that once you leave the spirit world...
就再也回不去了
you can never go back.
每天晚上 他都会仰望天空...
And every night, he looks up in the sky...
看着月亮并呼唤着她的名字
and sees the moon and howls her name.
可是...
But...
他们再也不能拥抱她了
he can never touch her again.
苦艾流苏被恶整了
Koo-koo-Kachooka got screwed.
是库埃阿苏
Kuekuatsheu.
原住民语是“金刚狼”的意思
Means the Wolverine.
怎么了 罗根?
What you're doing, Logan?
凯拉！
Kayla!
你不是这一带的 对吧?
You're not from around here, are you?
怎么看出来的?
What gave me away?
给你的酒馆上过保险了吗?
You got an insurance in this place?
保险?
Insurance?
没有
No.
那可糟了
Too bad.
看看 看看 看看... 看看谁大驾光临了
Well, well, well... Look what the cat dragged in.
伙计们 不管他是谁 带他出去
Guys, whatever this is, take it outside.
- 为什么? - 为什么?
- Why? - Why?
电话不打 信也不写
You don't call, you don't write.
还有什么办法能吸引你的注意力?
How else am I supposed to get your attention?
我真不想说出来 詹姆斯
I hate to say it, James.
坦白的说 我有点小失望
But, frankly, I'm a little disappointed.
住手
Stay down.
告诉我 吉米 她对你真的那么重要吗?
Tell me something, Jimmy, was she worth it?
你什么时候才能明白?
When are you gonna figure it out?
我们跟他们不同
We are not like them.
我... 不像你那么心狠手辣
I... am nothing like you.
当然
Sure you are.
你只是还不明白
You just don't know it yet.
- 发现什么了? - 他在酒吧里打架 几处刀伤
- What do we got? - Bar fight. Multiple knife wounds.
什么? 不是玩笑吧? 这家伙没事啊
What? Is this a joke? The guy's fine.
他在那?
Where is he?
- 告诉我他在那! - 我不知道你说的谁
- I said where is he! - I don't know who he is.
我能帮你
I can help you.
我来这6年了
Six years I've been here.
期间无人问津 你却突然出现
No one knew me and then you show up.
- 然后第二天 她就死了! - 我警告过你的
- And the next day, she's dead! - I tried to warn you.
为什么不告诉我是维克多?
Why don't you tell me it was Victor?
我也不知道
I didn't know.
我用我儿子的生命担保! 我真的...
I swear on my son's life! I didn't...
维克多的欲望不断膨胀
Victor's appetites were becoming too public.
所以我得把他关起来 他认为我出卖了他
I had to lock him up. He thought I'd betrayed him.
然后逃脱了
Went AWOL.
他说他不会放过我们中的任何一个人的
He said he was coming after all of us.
你不是来警告我的
You didn't come to warn me.
你是为了保住你自己
You came to save your own ass.
那你有什么计划 队长?
So what's your plan, captain?
罗根 你知道你打不贏他的
You can't beat him, Logan, you know you can't.
我会找到他杀死他的
I'm gonna find him and kill him.
我可以给你打败他的武器
I can give you the tools to defeat him.
- 借此我们也可以拯救他人 - 你是说拯救你自己吧?
- So we can still save the others. - You mean save yourself, right?
我答应你两件事:
I promise you two things:
你要忍受比常人更多的痛苦
You'll suffer more pain than any other man can endure,
但是你能完成复仇
but you'll have your revenge.
如果我跟你走 就是下定决心要复仇
If I come with you, I'm coming for blood.
不管法律和约束
No law, no code of conduct.
你给我指明方向 然后就他妈的滚开
You point me in the right direction and you get the hell out of my way.
手术一旦开始
When it starts,
无论你来此的理由是什么
whatever the reason is that you're doing this,
集中意念 也许这样能缓解痛苦
focus on that. Maybe it will help.
相信我 我已经历过比这糟糕的事情
Trust me, I've been through worse.
不 你还没有
No, you haven't.
准备就绪
We are ready.
你将会变得无坚不摧
We're gonna make you indestructible.
但首先 我们要摧毁一个旧的你
but first, we're gonna have to destroy you.
还记得 我们去非洲 要找的是什么吗?
Remember what we were looking for in Africa?
我记得
I remember.
我找到了
Well, I found it.
我们用它打造了一种... 强大的合金
It helped us create a... metal compound so strong
让你能承受住一切攻击
that you will be able to withstand virtually anything.
这就是阿德曼钢
It's called Adamantium.
罗根 我自己无法击倒维克多
I can't put Victor down myself, Logan.
想要杀了他 你得另辟蹊径
To kill him, you're gonna have to embrace the other side.
变成野兽
Become the animal.
开始吧
Let's do this.
我差点忘了
I almost forgot.
我要新的刻章
I want new ones.
你想要什么称号?
What do you want them to say?
金刚狼
Wolverine.
将军们! 欢迎
Generals! Welcome.
孟森将军
General Munson.
今天 我们将见证医学史的新纪元
Today, we're gonna witness medical history.
- 今天 我们将创造X战警 - X?
- Today, we're gonna create Weapon X. - X?
罗马数字的十
Roman numeral, Ten.
我们会把阿德曼钢 与X战警的骨骼 融合起来
We are about to begin bonding Adamantium to Weapon X's skeleton.
开始吧
Let's begin.
- 我们是兄弟 吉米 - 罗根!
- We're brothers, Jimmy. - Logan!
体温华氏108度 并持续升高
Body temperature is 1-0-8 and rising.
他为什么在狂抖? 不应该是安安静静的么?
Why is he thrashing like that? Why isn't he sedated?
他很痛苦 就像我们一样
He feels pain, just like the rest of us.
麻醉药对他不管用
Anaesthesia won't work on him.
所以他必须是自愿接受实验
That's why he had to volunteer.
心率190次/分 195
190, 195.
- 他能活下来么? - 我不知道
- Will he survive this? - I don't know.
心率200次/分
200.
我的儿子
son.
心跳速度远超最大负荷
Heartbeat's well beyond maximum.
- 血压? - 260/180
- Blood pressure? - 260 on 180.
他能熬过去 他可以的
He can make it, he can make it.
维克多
Victor!
我爱你
I love you.
你不是野兽 罗根
You're not an animal, Logan.
意思就是... 金刚狼
It means... the Wolverine.
我猜他会死
I guess he can die.
快点 老伙计 醒过来
Come on, old friend. Come back.
心率上升
Heart rate rising.
阿德曼钢蓄水池已枯竭
Adamantium reservoir is depleted.
没有排斥反应 实验成功
No rejection. Procedure completed.
我们成功了!
We did it!
要把他带到岛上么?
We take him to the island?
岛上? 不
The island? No.
融合起作用了
The bonding works.
我们要用他的DNA创造下一代XI战警
We use his DNA for the XI.
清除他的记忆
Erase his memory.
我想他听见了你说的话
I think he heard you.
一级防范!
Lockdown!
捉到他 取下他的首级
Hunt him down. Take his head off.
老公
Travis!
我想谷仓里有个裸男
I think there is some naked man in the barn.
没错
Yep.
孩子...
Son...
你究竟在这里做什么?
What in hell are you doing?
- 我很冷 - 冷?
- It's cold. - Cold?
- 你没有穿衣服 - 是的
- You got no clothes on. - Yeah.
你没有吸毒 对吧?
You're not onto drugs, are you?
是的
No.
只是度过了一个糟糕的夜晚
You just had a rough night.
是的 可以这么说
Yeah, you could say that.
到房子里来
Come on up the house.
我儿子有一些旧衣服 也许你能穿得下
Some of my son's old clothes will probably fit you.
接着 盖好身子
Here, cover it up with that.
我可不想老太太 被你吓得心脏病发作
I don't want to give an old lady a heart attack.
你在里面还好吗?
You're right in there?
是的 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
晚餐已经摆上桌了
Supper's on the table.
我... 好的 我马上就过去
I... Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
我发誓我会赔偿的
I swear I'm gonna pay for it.
放那边吧
Set it down over there.
过来坐下 孩子
Come and sit down, son.
十分感激你们... 为我做的一切
I can't thank you both enough... for everything.
把你留在外面受冻 是很不得体的
It wouldn't have been decent to leave you out there to freeze.
- 得体... - 什么?
- Decent... - What?
嗯... 没什么 我只是还不习惯这个词
Um... Nothing, I'm just not really used to that word.
外面那机车不错
That's a nice chopper you've got out there.
你是说摩托车?
You know motorcycle?
哦 天啊 又说这个!
Oh Lord, here we go!
我最喜欢的是1948年的盘状头发动机
My favorite is a '48 Panhead.
我买过一辆刚出厂的新车
I bought one new off the line.
那时候你还很小呢 孩子
I think you're a little young for that, son.
你一定是累坏了 今晚睡好点
You must be exhausted. You get a good night's sleep.
睡在谷仓
In the barn.
那里可没什么东西 能让你打坏了
Nothing you can break out there.
我爱你
I love you.
- 为什么月儿如此孤寂? - 为什么?
- Why is the moon so lonely? - Why?
因为她有过一个爱人
Because she used to have a lover.
他却永远不能拥抱着她
He can never touch her again.
睡的可好?
You sleep ok?
嗯... 是的
Uh... yeah.
你看起来 像是要去做一件坏事
You look like a man fixing to do a bad thing.
知道那些想要复仇的人 结局会怎样吗?
You know what happens to man looking for blood?
- 会怎样? - 他们都能复仇
- What? - They find it.
- 我们都有其他的选择 孩子 - 是的 但我的主意已定
- We all got a choice, son. - Yeah, mine got taken.
胡说
Bullshit.
这是我儿子的夹克
This was my son's jacket.
穿上试试
Try it on.
- 多谢 - 不客气...
- Thank you. - Yep...
你想骑我的车去兜几圈 测试减震系统
You wanna take my bike for a spin, test the suspension.
1964年 哈?
'64, huh?
哇 你真沉
Man, you're heavy.
是的 最近重了一些
Yeah, I put on a little weight recently.
早上好
Good morning.
噢 你穿上太合身了!
Oh, it fits you beautifully!
我给你带来些...
I brought you some...
X战警在谷仓 他刚害死了两个平民
Weapon X is in the barn. He just murdered two civilians.
把他炸成碎片 看他还能不能活下来
Blow him to bits. Let's see if he can survive that.
来接我!
Come and get me!
把他的脑袋炸开花
Blow his brains all over the road.
该死!
Damn!
A-1小队 别把他跟丢了!
Alpha One, do not lose him!
A-2小队 目标正向你靠近!
Alpha 2, target's coming to you!
拉高!
Pull up!
撤退 撤退
Pull back! Pull back!
零号特工?
Zero?
Zero man?
零号特工?
Zero?
零号特工 罗根死了没?
Zero, is Logan dead?
不知道 我坠机了
Don't know, I'm down.
零号特工 他死了吗 罗根死了吗?
Zero, was he dead, is Logan dead?
零号特工 回话!
Zero, come in!
你企图杀我
You tried to kill me.
罗根？
Logan?
维克多在哪?
Where is Victor?
回基地来
Come back to base.
我会解释一切 我们一起拿下维克多
I'll explain everything, we'll take Victor down together.
回答错误
Wrong answer.
我杀了维克多之后 就会去杀你
After I've killed Victor, I'm coming for you.
罗根 听着
Logan, listen to me.
如果你这样走下去 你会后悔你所看到的
If you go down this road, you're not gonna like what you find.
是你想要头野兽的 上校?
You wanted the animal, Colonel?
你得到了
You got it.
这些都是好人
Those were good people back there.
无辜的人
Innocent people.
有趣的是 无辜的好人往往都因你而死
It's funny how good innocent people tend to die around you.
零号特工根本没有机会还击
Zero never stood a chance.
唯一能制伏罗根的只有阿德曼钢子弹
The only thing that'll take him down is an Adamantium bullet
实验室已经被破坏了 准备撤离
This facility is compromised. Prep transport.
这快变成一场灾难了
Colonel, this is turning into a disaster.
- 别担心 我们会阻止罗根的 - 你确定?
- Don't worry, we'll stop him. - Really?
为了使他坚不可摧...
You've just spent half a billion dollars...
你已经花了五亿美元了
making him indestructible.
- 长官? - 什么
- Sir? - Yes.
您要找的小变种人 我们已经找到了
The young mutant you've been looking for, we found him.
将军 罗根可不是我们唯一的棋子
General, Logan isn't the only piece in this puzzle.
我们得从实验室撤离
I need to evacuate this facility.
请您回华盛顿吧
Please, go back to Washington.
我们还有活要干
We've got work to do.
我说…你说…这个是
Yo hablo: I talk, tu hablas: you talk, el habla?
谁来翻译一下?
Somebody translate?
桑默斯？
Summers?
坐直了 把太阳镜摘了
Sit up and take off those glasses.
我头痛
I have a headache.
那放学后留堂就戴着你的眼镜
Then you can wear them in detention after school
然后把这个动词变位抄上一百遍
while you add up this conjugation 100 times.
有人能回答吗?
Somebody else?
他说
He talks.
很好 是他说的意思
Thank you, he talks. El habla.
(拉斯维加斯)
- 你确定是维克多？ - 对
- You sure it was Victor? - Yeah.
该死!
Damn!
我很抱歉 老兄
I'm sorry, mate.
我走之后他到底发生了什么?
What the hell happened to him after I left?
他变本加厉了
He got worse.
他觉得是你抛弃了他
He felt like you abandoned him.
见鬼 我们都这么认为
Hell, we all do.
但是维克多 他必须得证明他比你优秀
But Victor, he had to prove you he was better than you.
他觅寻猎物 想杀就杀
Hunting and killing everything's he was pointin' at.
几个月以后我受够了围捕他们
Quit a few months later myself, couldn't take rounding them up.
- 围捕谁? - 这个你别管
- Rounding who up? - Leave it alone.
围捕谁？
Rounding who up, John?
嘿! 真见鬼
Hey! God damn it, John!
我们猎捕自己的同类 罗根
We hunted our own kind, Logan.
在地下设有专门关押这些人的地方
There's a special place in hell for the things we did.
变种人?
Mutants?
为什么?
Why?
史崔克说我们要制造一个特别的人
Stryker'd say we would make a difference.
来保护我们不受侵害
Protecting people from the bad ones.
你准备怎样打败维克多 罗根？
How are you gonna take Victor down, Logan?
记得我们在非洲的事吗？
Remember that stuff in Africa?
是的 记得 那又怎样?
Yeah, I remember Africa, what about it?
见鬼!
Damn!
他们对你做了什么?
What'd they do to you?
别问了
Don't ask.
听着 零号特工说了关于一个岛的事
Listen, Zero said something about an island.
你知道这是怎么回事吗?
Does that mean anything to you?
不
Nope.
但也许杜克知道
But maybe Dukes knows.
- 他和零号特工走得很近 - 佛雷杜克？
- Him and Zero were real tight. - Fred Dukes?
- 他在哪? - 他就在这
- Where is he? - He's here.
- 那好 我们去和他谈谈 - 等等
- Well, let's go talk to him. - Hold on.
他四点之前是不会来的
He don't get in until around four.
但是我得提醒你...
But I gotta warn you...
他得了饮食障碍症
he developed a bit of eating disorder.
我们已经有了对策
We all got our coping mechanisms.
正敦促他减肥
I'm trying to whoop him back into shape.
不管你做什么 千万别提他的体重
Whatever you do, don't mention his weight
得了 佛雷 如果你想回到原样 就得动起来 伙计
Come on, Fred, if you want to get into shape, you gotta move, man.
我告诉过他得动起来
I told him he got to move.
佛雷杜克? 被困在怪物里? 那可不是佛雷
Fred Dukes? Trapped inside that creature? That ain't Fred.
嘿 友好点 伙计
Hey, be nice, man.
嘿 肥... 佛雷
Hey, Fat, Fred, um.
瞧 我可记得那姑娘85磅的样子 哈
See, I remember that girl when she's got 85 pounds, huh.
噢 这可真有趣 你还是那么有意思 罗根
Oh that's funny. You're still so funny, Logan.
你知道维克多在哪吗?
You know where Victor is?
不知道
No idea.
那个岛又是什么 瘦小子?
What's the island, slim?
出去的时候可别让门撞了你 罗根
Don't let the door hit you on the way out, Logan.
听着 你不告诉我维克多在哪 我是不会走的
Listen, I ain't gonna leave until you tell me where Victor is.
拜托 老大 帮个忙
Come on, Bob. For old times' sake, huh?
你刚才是不是叫我...
Did you just call me...
大胖子?
Blob?
不 只是...
No, but...
我告诉过你别提他的体重
I told you not to mention his weight.
你为什么叫他大胖子?
Why did you call him Blob?
我没叫他大胖子 我叫的是老大!
I didn't call him Blob, I said Bob!
真该死!
Goddamn it!
我有个主意
I got an idea.
- 这就是你的主意? - 我在试着帮你 罗根
- This is your idea of an idea? - Trying to help you out, Logan.
杜克并不太喜欢你 这你知道
Dukes don't like you that much, and you know it.
同感
The feeling is mutual.
用这双手套 伙计 和他小跳一段
Use those gloves, man, dance with him a little bit.
让他在你身上撒撒气
Allow him to let his anger out on you.
我觉得如果你这么做...
I figure if you do that...
没准他会告诉你的
he might tell you everything you wanna know.
得了 伙计 你瞧他那样
Come on, man, look at him.
上衣都快遮不住他那圆滚滚的肚子了
Big old ass comin' out of the front of his shirt.
天啊 看在上帝的份上 他像快心脏病发了
Jesus, he's gonna have a coronary for Christ's sake.
这有够大的担架...
Is there even a stretcher big enough...
把他抬出去吗?
to take this guy out of here?
我倒不担心他会被担架抬走
It ain't him I'm worried about getting out on a stretcher.
- 你这混蛋 - 来吧 罗根
- You're an asshole. - Come on, Logan
揍他!
Whoop his ass!
如果你想要这个
If you want.
这算什么 你想和我跳舞吗?
What's that suppose to be. You wanna dance with me?
噢 噢 这可真棒
Oh. Oh, that feels good.
嘿 你猜怎么着?
Hey, guess what?
瞧 他会说的 伙计
See, he's gonna talk, man.
你把他伺候好了 他自然会说的
You got him right where you want him.
- 你到底站在哪一边? - 来吧
- Whose side are you on anyway? - come on.
来吧 我们继续
Come on now, let's up.
该死！
Damn it!
现在 说 维克多在哪?
Now, where is Victor?
不觉得戴太阳镜会看不清吗?
A little dark for sunglasses, don't you think?
求求你 不要！求求你 不要！
Please don't! Please! Don't, please!
维克多！
Victor!
维克多在哪?
Where's Victor?
维克多和... 和史崔克在... 在岛上...
Victor's... with Stryker on... on the island...
他们... 他们一起管理那
they... they run it together.
什... 什么?
What... what?
维克多和史崔克在一起?
Victor's being with Stryker?
是的
Yeah.
你不知道?
You didn't know that?
现在剩下的就只有罗根了 我...
All that's left now is Logan, I...
... 我相信你能办好这事
... trust you can handle that.
我以前也做过 不是吗?
I did before, didn't I?
噢 对 你以前做过
Oh yes, you did that.
我们的交易... 依然有效 对吗?
Our deal... it still applies, right?
当然
Of course.
现在把他捆起来 贴上标签 上尉
Now pack him and tag him, Captain.
那个岛是用来做什么的?
What's the island?
是... 维克多逮捕他们之后 史崔克就带他们去那
It's where... Stryker takes them after Victor's caught 'em.
等等 等等... 嗯 什么? 带谁去?
Wait, wait... um, what? Takes who?
变种人
Mutants.
有传闻说史崔克拿他们做实验
The rumor is that Stryker's doing experiments on them there.
嗯 你不会好奇在他们身上发生了什么?
Well, you never wondered what happened to them?
我试过不去想
I tried not to.
他们杀了她...为了报仇我才同意把阿德曼钢植入我体内
They killed her...so I'd let them put Adamantium in me.
他们杀了她就为这该死的实验
They killed her for a goddamn experiment.
那岛在哪?
Where is it?
史崔克对此极为保密
Logan, Stryker kept it real secret.
但是...
But...
- 有人从那逃了出来 - 谁?
- A prisoner escaped there once. - Who?
他叫雷米勒伯
His name is Remy LeBeau.
他曾经是新奥尔良的街头骗子
He was a street hustler from New Orleans.
监狱守卫叫他金牌手
The guards at the prison called him Gambit
因为玩扑克牌他赢光了他们所有的钱...
because he kept taking all their money at poker...
我就知道这些
that's all I know.
史崔克想怎样 他的最终目的是什么？
What's Stryker up to, Fred, what's the end game?
史崔克想要他们的力量 然后把力量集中起来
He's taking their powers, trying to combine them somehow.
我就知道 罗根 我就知道这些
It's all I know, Logan. It's all I know.
如果我还得回来 那你的脑袋就得搬家
If I had to come back here, I'm gonna take your head off.
我和你一起去 罗根
I'm coming with you, Logan.
- 我可不是去救赎什么的 - 我也没这打算
- There's no redemption where I'm going. - I ain't asking.
那就是我们要找的人
There's our dude.
那太酷了
That's cool.
我去把门 免得他跑了
But I'm gonna go and cover the back if he runs.
我可不想和他打架
I'm not havin' a fight with him.
- 对 是这样 - 什么?
- Yeah right. - What?
我跟每个人都打架吗?
I am havin' fights with everybody?
狗不是总和猫厮杀吗?
Don't dogs kill cats?
你去后面望风吧?
Just go cover the back, will ya?
你是雷米勒伯？
Are you Remy LeBeau?
我欠你钱?
Do I owe you money?
没有
No.
那么我就是雷米勒伯
Then Remy LeBeau I am.
大盲注一百 小盲注五十
Large blind is 100, and the small blind's 50.
你也来玩玩?
May I deal you in?
17块能玩吗?
Now what can I get for 17 bucks?
17块?
17 dollars?
也许够叫辆出租车回家
A cab ride home, perhaps.
你是我弟弟的新保姆吗 约翰?
You're my brother's new babysitter, John?
我不是布莱德
I ain't Bradley, Victor.
而且你那件黑大衣也吓不到我
And your creepy black coat don't scare me.
真的吗?
Really?
杜克就吃这套
It worked on Dukes.
真抱歉 因为我现在就要杀了你...
What a shame, 'cause now I'm gonna kill you...
那么罗根就没有机会了
so Logan never gets the chance.
是哪阵风把您给吹来了 先生?
So what brings you to our fair city, sir?
维克多里德?
Victor Creed.
那是谁?
And who's that?
我要杀的人
The man I'm gonna kill.
他帮一个叫史崔克的人工作 在一座岛上
He works for a man named Stryker on, uh, on an island.
- 我只要知道岛在哪里 - 你以为我会知道?
- I just need to know where it is. - Why would you think I know that?
因为我知道你是谁 金牌手
Well, 'cause I know who you are, Gambit.
你能从那逃出来...
You are the guy who escaped...
所以你也能带我过去
and you are the guy who's gonna take me back there.
知道吗 约翰...
You know, John...
我一直想告诉你个事
There's something I always wanted to tell you.
你很容易判断
You're predictable.
我感觉得到你的脊椎 可爱的约翰
I can feel your spine, Johnny Boy.
怪了，我不知道你还有脊椎
That's funny. I never knew you had one.
你的胸牌不错啊 先生
Those are mighty nice tags you have on there, sir.
跟抓走我的那人戴的一样
The men who took me wore tags just like 'em.
老大 听我说...
Hey, now Bob, you listen to me...
我在那个炼狱里待了两年...
Two years I was rottin' in that hell...
我绝不回去
and I'm never going back.
噢 真亮啊
Oh, shiny.
跟我聊聊 吉米
Tell me something, Jimmy.
你知道怎样才能杀了我吗?
Do you even know how to kill me?
把你的头切下来
I'm gonna cut your goddamn head off.
你试试
See if that works.
你迟钝了 老头
You're gettin' slow, old man.
你这个畜生
Son of a bitch.
你得为她的死付出代价
You're gonna die for what you did to her.
维克多
Victor!
这棍法真漂亮
That's a nice stick.
痞子 你听好了
Shithead. Here's the deal.
带我去那个岛 我要杀了史崔克
See, you're gonna take me to this island, where I can kill Creed, Stryker
还有所有你憎恶的人
pretty much everyone you hate in this world.
明白吗?
Do you understand?
你真要杀了他们
You really want to kill 'em.
只要你别碍事
As long as you stay out of my way, yeah.
上校
Colonel.
将军?
General?
这就是XI武器?
Is this Weapon XI?
集众之长 避众之短
All their strenghts but none of their weaknesses.
你很讨厌他们 不是吗?
You really hate them, don't you?
不 不是讨厌
No, I don't hate them.
跟他们打了20年的交道...
After 20 years of working with them...
我很清楚他们的破坏力
I just know what they can do.
如果让战争在开始前就结束...
If we win this war before it starts...
就能拯救无数生命
and save countless lives in the process.
先发制人是唯一途径 将军
Preemptive action is the only action here, General.
我们国家再也不能坐视不管
The days of our country sitting on the sidelines are over.
我们要提前进攻...
We need to take the fight to the enemy...
在敌人打过来之前
before they take the fight to us.
- 我欣赏你的激情 真的 - 谢谢
- I admire your passion, I do. - Thank you.
但到此为止了
But this is as far as it goes.
X武器是个... 败笔
Weapon X was a... a hickup.
我们知道你儿子比尔的事了
We know about your son, Bill.
我们知道他变异了
We know he's a mutant.
也知道他杀了你的妻子
And we know he killed your wife.
你不该向我们隐瞒
You shouldn't have kept that from us.
这...
That...
- 这与我的工作毫无关系 - 胡说
- That has nothing to do with my work. - Bullshit.
你无法逃脱干系 我想你明白
You're too close to this. I'm sure you know it.
你说得对 我... 我承认
You're right. I... I won't lie to you.
我的儿子影响了我的家庭
My son did bring the problem home for me.
但我发誓...
But I took an oath...
要保证民众的安全
to protect the American people
任何威胁也别想阻止我
from every threat,
无论是外部
both foreign
... 还是内部
... and domestic.
- 晕机吗 嗯? - 我没事
- You don't like flying, huh? - I'm fine.
做好你的事
Just concentrate on what you're doing.
真没事? 你看你全身都汗湿了
You sure? You got a bit of sweat on your brow there.
真好笑 你只管好好看路...
Very funny, just keep your eyes on the...
看啥? 看云么?
On the what? Clouds?
飞机上上下下像个悠悠球
We're jumpin' up and down like a freakin' yoyo here.
你从哪找来这个?
Where did you get this thing anyway?
噢 这可是我的宝贝 一个比赛赢来的
Oh, this is my baby, I won her in a game.
- 爪子游戏 - 棒极了
- Jacks over fives. - Great.
放松点 快到了
Relax. We're almost there.
那就是了 那座小岛
There it is. The island.
3公里的岛 什么也藏不住
Three Mile Island. Hiding in plain sight.
没人能潜入核电站
No one's gonna sneak around a nuclear reactor.
他们害怕被变成怪物
They think it's gonna turn them into freaks.
像你一样?
Like you?
没错
Right.
准备好了么?
All right, you ready?
再不跳就没机会了 我们走
Cause it's now or never. Let's go.
等不及了
About time.
嗨 这真能让你变的舒服...
Hey, if it's make you feel any better...
我觉得会疼死
this is really gonna hurt.
其实 这是必然的
Oh yeah, it kind of does actually.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你也是
Likewise.
妈的
Oh shit.
怎么样了?
How are you doing?
一切正常吗?
Is everything alright?
- 还要多久? - 几个小时
- Is he ready yet? - A few hours.
他会听从我的命令吧?
He will respond to my commands?
是的 上校
Yes, Colonel.
罗根
Logan
欢迎回到战场
Welcome back to the war.
在我把你开膛破肚之前 告诉我这到底是为什么
Before I gut you, I wanna know why.
我需要将你们的能量传输给"死侍"
I needed your powers for the pool.
什么?
For the what?
变种人克星 "死侍"
A mutant killer. The dead pool.
这么多年的研究 就是了为寻找...
Years of searching him, to find him...
寻找一种完美的能量...
finding the right powers...
他们能和谐共存而不会相互排斥
that can coexist in one body without ripping it apart.
我儿子是拼图的第一块
My son was the first piece of the puzzle.
罗根 而你是最后一块
Logan, you are the last.
你们完成了XI
You made Weapon XI possible.
我...
I...
我想让你帮忙...
I asked you to help but...
可你却只想平静的生活
you said you wanted the quiet life.
是的...
Well...
你让我看到了前所未有的动力...
I've learned that nothing motivates...
一个男人为了家人而复仇
the men in your family like revenge.
你是谁?
Who are you?
她可是你的老朋友啊
Oh, she's a real old friend.
你以为我们会让你就这样离开吗?
Do you really think we'd just let you walk away?
你很危险
You are a dangerous man.
我会紧盯危险人物的
I like to keep an eye on dangerous men.
告诉他你的死是怎么回事
Tell him about the day you died.
他们给我打了一剂盐酸噻嗪
They gave me a shot of hydrochloride thiazide.
它会让心率变的非常慢...
It reduces the heart rate so low...
就像死了一样
it appears you flatline.
别生她的气
Don't be angry with her.
相当受用... 对你们种群来说
Real credit... to your species.
知道吗 她妹妹的...
Did you know that her sister...
皮肤坚不可摧?
has diamond-hard skin?
凯拉的能力是触碰催眠
Kayla's mutation is tacto-hypnosis.
她只要碰触别人 就能左右他们思想
She can influence people as long as she touches them.
是很好的引诱工具
Quite a useful tool in the seduction.
朋友 从来都是虚幻
It was never real, my friend.
对我来说 真真切切
It was real for me.
我说过 选择这条路...
I told you if you came down this road...
你不会喜欢所发现的
you wouldn't like what you'd found.
你给我讲的...
That story you told me...
关于男人采花献给月儿的故事...
about man who gets flowers for the moon...
我给改编了
I had it backwards.
我本以为你是月儿 我是你的金刚狼
I thought you were the moon and I was your Wolverine.
但结果你却是个骗子 不是吗?
But you were the Trickster, aren't you?
我只是被你耍的白痴
I am just the fool that got played.
最糟的是 我本该知道
The worst part of this is I should have known.
我却忽略了直觉
But I ignored my instincts.
忘记了我是谁
I ignored what I really am.
这种事再不会有了
Well, that will never happen again.
- 上校 - 现在不行
- Colonel. - Not now, Kayla.
你要求的 我都做到了
I have done everything you've asked.
我妹妹...
My sister...
你说过如果我帮你 你就放了她
You said that if I help you, you'd let her go.
凯拉 事情可没那么简单
Kayla, it's not as simple as that.
她的变异很独特 非常美丽
Her mutation is unique. Quite beautiful.
我们只需要多点时间来分析 仅此而已
We just need a little more time to analyze it, that's all.
你放他走了?
You let him go?
- 维克多 别这样 - 你不能放他走
- Victor, please. - You can't let him go.
- 你打不赢他的 - 给我注射阿德曼钢
- You can't beat him, Victor. - Give me the Adamantium.
- 测试结果... - 都说好了!
- Tests came out... - We had a deal!
你撑不过那个手术
You would never survive the operation.
他能受得了我也能
I can take anything he can.
你不能
No, you can't.
你是我最钟爱的战士 维克多
You are my favorite soldier, Victor.
耐心点 会有时机的
Be patient, time will come.
他在利用我们!
He's using us!
这次怎么样 来真格的?
How about this time, you die for real?
放开我
Let me go.
你的小伎俩对我没用
Your mind game don't work on me.
维克多
Victor!
感觉不错吧?
Feels good, doesn't it?
怒火中烧...
All that rage...
来呀
Do it.
罗根
Logan!
你不是野兽
You're not an animal.
你是
Oh yes, you are.
下手吧
Do it.
干掉我
Finish it.
罗根？
Logan?
我的妹妹
My sister.
他们抓了我妹妹
They have my sister.
相信我 我没有迷惑你
Please, I didn't trick you into believing me.
对我来说也是真的
It was real for me too.
求你了 对不起
Please, I'm so sorry.
他们抓了我妹妹
They have my sister.
她在哪?
Where is she?
激活11号武器
Activate Weapon XI.
熔接还没完成
The binding process is incomplete.
照做就是了!
Just do it!
快!
Now!
你没事吧? 快走
Are you okay? Come on.
好...
Okay...
太完美了
Perfect.
- 凯拉 把孩子们带走 - 罗根...
- Kayla, get these kids out of here. - Logan...
另找出口
Find another way out.
快 我们走!
Come on, let's go!
韦德 是你吗?
Wade, is that you?
史崔克 终于让你闭嘴了
I guess Stryker finally figured out how to shut you up.
(战斗)
韦德
Wade...
你不必这样
You don't have to do this.
既然非要动手...
Alright, maybe you do.
来人就开枪!
Shoot on sight!
我能行! 把我对着他们!
I can help! Point me at 'em!
快去!
Go!
开火! 快!
Go! Now!
打到了吗?
Did I get them?
没错
Yeah.
- 我们走 - 我不能走
- Let's go. - I can't go.
凯拉 快走!
Kayla, come on!
我得留下
I have to stay here.
你带他们走
You take them.
快走!
Go!
往左
Go left.
左
Left.
- 什么? - 我们得往左走
- What? - We go left.
- 你看不见的 - 相信我
- You can't see. - Trust me.
看你怎麼跳舞
C'mon Bob! Let's see your dance up here.
(斩首)
只有我才能杀你
Nobody kills you but me.
背对背!
Back-to-back!
- 他在这 - 不 在这
- I got him! - Oh no, you don't.
停!
Stop!
- 不是这条路 - 就是这条!
- This can't be the way. - This is the way!
- 你怎么知道? - 我就知道
- How do you know? - I just know.
快走
Come on.
阿德曼钢子弹
Adamantium bullets.
打穿他的厚脑壳 看他还怎么愈合
Let's see him heal with a few of these through his thick skull.
你阻止不了他 用那个也没用
You can't stop him. Even with that.
他还是会愈合
He'll heal.
大脑会愈合
His brain may heal.
但记忆却回不来了
But his memories won't grow back.
这改变不了我们的关系
This doesn't change anything between us, Victor.
我们一刀两断了
We're done.
我们是断不开的 吉米
We can never be done, Jimmy.
我们是兄弟
We're brothers.
兄弟会互相扶持
Brothers look out for each other.
- 想我了? - 老天...
- You miss me? - Jesus...
你说过要杀了所有人...
When you said you'd gonna kill everyone...
我以为你在吹牛
I thought you may just've been exaggerating.
是呀...
Yeah...
我像吹牛的人吗?
Do I look like a man who exaggerates?
甭客气
You're welcome.
那些孩子正设法逃离这个岛
These kids trying to get off the island.
- 分头行动 快! - 这就去
- Split up. Go! - I'm on it.
凯拉！
Kayla!
我爱你
I love you.
不...
No...
我好冷
I am so cold.
听着 我要带你走
Listen to me, I'm gonna get you outta here.
明白吗?
You understand?
我们不着急 慢慢来
Let's go easy, nice and easy.
好
That's it.
就这样
我带你走
I'm gonna get you out.
罗根！
Logan!
我本该让你开枪的
I should make you pull the trigger.
但那和你就没什么两样了
But that would make us not better than you.
扔掉枪
Throw the gun away.
转身
Turn around.
走到你双脚流血
Walk until your feet bleed.
再接着走
And then keep walking.
没事了 史考特
It'll be all right, Scott.
我是X教授
My name is Charles Xavier.
和你们一样 我也是变种人
I'm a mutant, like you.
- 我能听见你的想法 - 是 我也能听见你的
- I can hear your thoughts. - Yes. And I can hear yours.
你们安全了
You're safe now.
来 我们走吧
Come. We have to go.
(金刚狼)
孩子们安全了
The kids are safe.
怎么了?
What the hell happened?
- 你是谁? - 你什么意思 我是谁?
- Who are you? - What do you mean, who am I?
是我把你带到这儿的 现在该走了
I'm the guy who brought you here. Now we gotta go.
我到底在哪?
Where the hell am I?
听着 我是你的朋友
Listen to me, I am a friend.
你的朋友
I'm a friend.
我叫什么?
What's my name?
我叫什么!
What's my name!
你叫罗根
Your name is Logan.
你得相信我 我们必须得走
You need to trust me. We have to go.
跟我来
Follow me.
快!
Now!
你认识她吗?
Do you know her?
不认识
No.
那些家伙可不会喜欢你的所作所为
These dudes are not gonna like what you've done in this place.
我们必须要走了
We really need to go.
我自己走
I'll find my own way.
好运
Good luck.
史崔克上校?
Colonel Stryker?
- 威廉史崔克上校? - 是的
- Colonel William Stryker? - Yes.
孟森将军死亡一案
You're wanted for questioning...
我们要询问你一些问题
in connection of the death of General Munson.
长官
Sir.